http://www.aephi.org/privacy-tscs

News Archive
Privacy, Ts&CsThese Terms of Use apply to our website, and mobile versions of our website and mobile sites (collectively, the “Site”) that expressly adopt, display, or link to these Terms of Use, as may be revised from time to time.The Site is operated by Alpha Epsilon Phi Sorority, Inc. and Alpha Epsilon Phi Foundation (collectively, “AEPhi” or “we” or “us” or “our”).Certain portions of the website, all or portions of certain microsites, and/or all or portions of certain mobile versions of the website and mobile sites may be separately dedicated to, partitioned for, or segregated for purposes of information or uses pertaining specifically to Alpha Epsilon Phi Foundation.For clarification, any websites, microsites, or social media pages operated by or for any AEPhi member, chapter, establishment, alumnae, or other group, or collections of one or more of the foregoing, are not officially associated with or endorsed by AEPhi, and AEPhi explicitly disclaims any and all responsibility and liability for the accuracy, content, and availability of information at such other sites and pages.Subject to these Terms of Use, the Site is offered to you (the “User” or “you”) for your use.  PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SITE.  Your use of the Site constitutes your agreement to be bound by these Terms of Use and AEPhi’s Privacy Policy, which is incorporated herein by reference.  If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, the Privacy Policy, or any other applicable terms, then do not use the Site.CONTENTAll Site content, including, without limitation, all text, graphics, design elements, audio, video, music, icons, images, hyperlinks, displays, products, HTML and any other code, scripts, and software, and the collection, arrangement, and assembly of the foregoing (collectively, the “Content”), is the property of AEPhi or its sponsors, distributors, or licensors, and is protected by copyright law and other U.S. and international laws and treaties.  The User is granted no right, title, or interest in or to the Content other than the limited license expressly set forth in these Terms of Use.
The User may not modify, publish, transmit, participate in the transfer or sale of, reproduce, create derivative works from, distribute, perform, display, incorporate into a website, or in any way exploit the Content, or any portion thereof, without the express prior written permission of AEPhi.ACCEPTABLE USEThe User’s permitted licensed use of the Site and Content is limited to the standard functionality of the Site.  In no event may the Site be used in a manner that: (i) is unlawful, fraudulent, or deceptive; (ii) harasses, abuses, stalks, threatens, defames, or otherwise infringes or violates the rights of any third party (including, without limitation, the rights of publicity or other proprietary rights); (iii) uses technology or other means not authorized by AEPhi to access Content; (iv) attempts to introduce viruses or any other computer code, files, or programs that interrupt, destroy, or limit the functionality of any computer software, hardware, or telecommunications equipment; (v) attempts to gain unauthorized access to AEPhi’s systems or user accounts; (vi) encourages conduct that would constitute a criminal offense or that gives rise to civil liability; (vii) attempts to damage, disable, or overburden AEPhi’s servers or networks; or (viii) fails to comply with applicable third-party terms.  The User must comply with all applicable third-party terms of use or terms of service (e.g., wireless carrier terms of service) at all times while using the Site.
AEPhi reserves the right to, in its sole discretion, terminate this limited license granted to the User hereunder and/or bring legal action against the User if the User engages in, or AEPhi reasonably believes the User has engaged in or is engaging in, use that violates these Terms of Use.
AEPhi’s failure or delay in taking such actions does not constitute a waiver of its rights to enforce these Terms of Use.Without the prior written consent of AEPhi, you or third parties acting on your behalf are not allowed to mirror or deep-link to the Site, use AEPhi’s proprietary marks as meta tags or keyword search terms, or use frames or utilize techniques or technologies to enclose any Content included on the Site.COMMENTSAll comments, feedback, suggestions, and ideas submitted, offered, or otherwise provided to AEPhi via the Site or in connection with your use of the Site (collectively, “Comments”) shall be and remain property of AEPhi.  AEPhi shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any Comments for any purpose whatsoever.USER INFORMATIONSome features that may be available on the Site require the transmission of information provided by the User (“User Information”).  The User agrees to keep the User Information provided to the Site current at all times and to promptly update such information to the extent of any change.  By using such features, the User consents to the transmission of User Information to AEPhi and/or its agents and authorizes AEPhi and/or its agents to record, process, and store such User Information as necessary for the Site functionality and for the purposes described herein and in the Privacy Policy.USER PARTICIPATION AND SUBMISSIONSThe Site may permit you to voluntarily submit, upload, and/or post content, including photographs, videos, comments, materials, and other user-generated content (collectively, “Submissions”).AEPhi may not review communications or Submissions posted to or created by users accessing the Site and is not in any manner responsible for the content of such communications or Submissions.  You acknowledge that, by providing you with the ability to view and distribute Submissions on the Site, AEPhi is merely acting as a passive conduit for such distribution and is not undertaking any obligation or liability relating to any such Submissions or activities on the Site.  However, AEPhi reserves the right to block or remove communications or Submissions that AEPhi determines to be in violation of these Terms of Use or otherwise unacceptable to AEPhi, in its sole discretion.
AEPhi will have no obligations with respect to the Submissions.Providing such Submission constitutes your consent and grant to AEPhi of an unrestricted, non-exclusive, royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right and permission to reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, disclose, distribute, incorporate, create derivative works of, and otherwise use and exploit the Submissions and all data, images, sounds, text, and other things embodied therein (including your name, likeness, voice, and biographical information) for any purpose and in any form or media, without any further authorization by you.  You further agree that AEPhi is free to use any ideas, concepts, and know-how contained in any Submission.
No compensation will be paid with respect to the use of any Submission.
AEPhi is under no obligation to post or use any Submission that you may provide and may remove any Submission at any time in AEPhi’s sole discretion and without notice.You understand and agree that such Submissions may be accessed and viewed by others, including by the general public, and, whether or not such Submissions are published, AEPhi does not guarantee any confidentiality with respect to any Submissions.  You are solely responsible for your own Submissions and the consequences of publication on the Site or elsewhere.
We reserve the right to determine in our sole discretion whether each Submission is appropriate; whether it complies with these Terms of Use, our standards, and applicable law; and whether it may be posted or removed.By making a Submission, you warrant and represent that; (i) you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the Submission as described in this section, including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to make the Submission; (ii) the content of the Submission is accurate; (iii) the use of the content in your Submission does not violate any provisions of these Terms of Use and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and (iv) you will indemnify AEPhi for all claims and liabilities resulting from your Submission.You further agree that you will not submit any content or other material to the Site that is contrary to applicable local, national, or international laws and regulations.AEPhi does not endorse any content submitted by any User, or any opinion, recommendation, or advice expressed therein, and AEPhi expressly disclaims any and all liability in connection with such content.THIRD-PARTY CONTENTThe User understands and agrees that AEPhi does not control and is not responsible for any Content made available on the Site by other users.  The User’s use of, or reliance on, any information contained in such third-party Content is at the User’s sole risk.
Under no circumstances will AEPhi be liable for any such third-party Content or for any loss or damage resulting from the User’s use of, or reliance on, such third-party Content.LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITESThe Site may include links to third-party websites or other sites not operated by AEPhi.  These links are provided for the User’s convenience and in no way signify any endorsement of any such websites or other sites or the content thereof.  ACCESS TO ANY SUCH LINKED WEBSITE OR OTHER SITE IS AT THE USER’S OWN RISK, AND AEPHI WILL NOT HAVE ANY LIABILITY ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO SUCH WEBSITES, OTHER SITES, AND/OR THEIR CONTENT, OR FOR ANY DAMAGES OR LOSS CAUSED OR ALLEGED TO BE CAUSED BY OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY USE OF OR RELIANCE ON ANY SUCH CONTENT, OR FOR ANY GOODS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH ANY SUCH WEBSITES OR OTHER SITES.TRADEMARKS AND COPYRIGHTSAll Content on the Site is the exclusive property of and owned by AEPhi, its licensors, or its content providers.  The Site and its Content are a collective work and a compilation under the United States copyright laws and other copyright laws, such copyrights being owned by AEPhi.  All trademarks, service marks, and trade names are trademarks or registered trademarks of, and are proprietary to, AEPhi or other respective owners that have granted AEPhi the right or license to use such marks.  Nothing on the Site shall be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark, logo, or service mark displayed on the Site without the owner’s prior written permission.AEPhi reserves all rights not expressly granted in and to the Site and its Content.ELIGIBILITY; JURISDICTIONThe User represents and warrants that she or he: (i) is fully competent and able to enter into and abide by these Terms of Use; (ii) is not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a “terrorist support” country; and (iii) is not included on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties.  The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13.
AEPhi does not represent the Site is available or appropriate for use in other jurisdictions outside the United States and Canada.
Any access to or use of the Site from other jurisdictions is at the User’s sole risk, and the User is responsible for complying with all applicable local laws.NOTICES AND PROCEDURES FOR MAKING CLAIMS OF COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENTPursuant to Title 17, United States Code, Section 512(c)(2), notifications of claimed copyright infringement should be sent to the Site’s designated agent.  ALL INQUIRIES NOT RELEVANT TO OR NOT COMPLYING WITH THE FOLLOW PROCEDURE WILL RECEIVE NO RESPONSE.To be effective, your notification must (i) be in writing, (ii) be provided to the AEPhi designated copyright agent, and (iii) include ALL of the following:1.   A physical or electronic signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed;2.   Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed upon, or, if there are multiple copyrighted works, a representative list of such works;3.   Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to locate the material;4.   Information reasonably sufficient to permit the service provider to contact you, such as address, telephone number, and, if available, an electronic mail address at which the complaining party may be contacted;5.   A statement that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and6.   A statement that the information in the notification is accurate and, under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.Notices of claimed copyright infringement should be directed to:By email:  webmaster@aephi.org  By postal mail: 11 Lake Avenue Extension, Suite 1A, Danbury, CT 06811By phone: 203-748-0029THE PRECEDING INFORMATION IS PROVIDED EXCLUSIVELY FOR NOTIFYING AEPHI THAT YOUR COPYRIGHTED MATERIAL MAY HAVE BEEN INFRINGED.  ALL OTHER INQUIRIES, SUCH AS PRODUCT- OR SERVICE-RELATED QUESTIONS OR REQUESTS, OR QUESTIONS ON PRIVACY, WILL NOT RECEIVE A RESPONSE THROUGH THIS PROCESS.EQUITABLE RELIEFYou acknowledge and agree that breach of these Terms of Use will result in irreparable harm that would be difficult to measure; and, therefore, that upon any such breach or threat of such breach, AEPhi shall be entitled to seek injunctive or other appropriate equitable relief from any court of competent jurisdiction (without the necessity of proving actual damages or of posting bond), in addition to whatever remedies AEPhi may have at law, under these Terms of Use, or otherwise.DISCLAIMERSAEPHI AND ITS LICENSORS AND CONTRACTORS DO NOT WARRANT OR GUARANTEE THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR COMPLETENESS OF THE SITE OR THE SITE CONTENT OR REPRESENT THAT THE SITE OR THE SITE CONTENT IS ERROR-FREE OR CAPABLE OF OPERATING ON AN UNINTERRUPTED BASIS.  THE SITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” AND WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND.
TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWABLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ARE HEREBY DISCLAIMED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.  Some jurisdictions do not allow the disclaimer of implied warranties, and, in such jurisdictions, portions of the foregoing disclaimer may not apply to you.LIMITATIONS OF LIABILITY AND EXCLUSIONS OF DAMAGESuse of the site is at THE USER’S own risk.  TO THE FULLEST EXTENT ALLOWABLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, AEPHI AND ITS LICENSORS AND CONTRACTORS shall NOT be LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO: (i) use or misuse of the SITE OR the SITE Content; (ii) inability to access or use the SITE or the SITE Content; (iii) any loss or corruption of data or information submitted VIA the SITE; (iv) any communications or services provided by, or requested from, AEPhi via the site; or (v) ANY PERSONAL INJURY (INCLUDING DEATH) OR PROPERTY DAMAGE RESULTING FROM ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE SITE OR THE SITE CONTENT.  The foregoing limitations of liability and exclusions of damages shall apply whether the claim is based on warranty, contract, tort, or any other legal theory, and whether or not AEPhi is advised of the possibility of such damages.
Some jurisdictions do not allow the limitation or exclusion of incidental or consequential damages in certain circumstances, so portions of the above limitations or exclusions may not apply to you.INDEMNIFICATIONYou agree to indemnify, defend, and hold harmless AEPhi and its respective affiliated and related entities and their respective officers, directors, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, service providers, subcontractors, and suppliers from and against any and all claims, actions, suits, damages, losses, liabilities, expenses, and costs, including reasonable attorney’s fees and court costs, arising or resulting from your use of the Site or the Content or any violation of these Terms of Use.MODIFICATION OF THESE TERMS OF USEAEPhi may, without notice to you, at any time revise these Terms of Use and other information contained on the Site.  AEPhi may also make improvements or changes in the products, services, or programs described in the Site at any time without notice.  AEPhi reserves the right to modify, suspend, or discontinue any aspect of the Site at any time.
Your continued use of the Site after any changes to these Terms of Use or other policies means you accept the changes.  You are responsible for regularly reviewing these Terms of Use.GOVERNING LAW; VENUEThese Terms of Use are governed by the laws of the State of Connecticut and applicable federal laws of the United States of America, without giving effect to conflict of laws principles.The User irrevocably consents to the exclusive jurisdiction of the federal and state courts situated in Danbury, Connecticut, USA, for purposes of any legal action arising out of or related to these Terms of Use or use of the Site.LEGAL NOTICE FOR NEW JERSEY RESIDENTSUnder the New Jersey Truth-in-Consumer Contract, Warranty and Notice ACT (“TCCWNA”), N.J.S.A. 56:12-14 et seq., consumers may not be offered any written contract which includes any provision that violates any clearly established legal right of a consumer, or responsibility of a seller, as established by state or federal law.  In addition, under the TCCWNA, no consumer contract may state that any of its provisions are or may be void, unenforceable or inapplicable in some jurisdictions without specifying which provisions are or are not void, unenforceable or inapplicable in New Jersey.  Therefore, the following provisions of these Terms of Use shall not be applicable to New Jersey residents: (1) the provisions concerning limiting our liability for any loss or damage is not applicable to New Jersey residents to the extent AEPhi was negligent or has breached its obligation; (2) the provisions concerning the exclusion or limitation of certain damages is not applicable to New Jersey residents with respect to punitive damages, loss of data, and loss of or damage to property; and (3) the provisions concerning the indemnification by the User is not applicable to New Jersey residents unless you were negligent or have breached these Terms of Use.GENERALThese Terms of Use shall apply to and bind your permitted assignees and successors in interest and those of AEPhi.  Amendments to these Terms of Use will become effective when posted on the Site.
Your continued use of the Site after such posting will be deemed your acceptance of these changes to these Terms of Use.  The waiver by AEPhi of any breach or default shall not be deemed to be a waiver of any later breach or default.
The exercise or failure to exercise any remedy shall not preclude the exercise of that remedy at another time or of any other remedy at any time.  If any provision or portion of these Terms of Use is held invalid or unenforceable, the other provisions and portions shall not be affected.
The headings are used for the convenience of the parties and shall not affect the construction or interpretation of these Terms of Use.HOW TO CONTACT AEPHIIf you have any questions or comments about these Terms of Use or the Site, please contact us:By email:  webmaster@aephi.org  By postal mail: 11 Lake Avenue Extension, Suite 1A, Danbury, CT 06811By phone: 203-748-0029PRIVACY POLICYLast Updated on:  March 27, 2019This Privacy Policy is intended to assist you in understanding what information we collect, how we use and share that information, and the safeguards we have in place for protecting this information.This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected online by Alpha Epsilon Phi Sorority, Inc., and/or Alpha Epsilon Phi Foundation (collectively, “AEPhi” or “we” or “us” or “our”) in connection with our website, microsites, and mobile versions of our website and mobile sites (collectively, the “Site”) that expressly adopt, display, or link to this Privacy Policy, as may be revised from time to time.It also applies to personal information AEPhi collects in connection with its pages on social media sites, such as Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, or others (collectively referred to as our “Social Media Pages”).By providing information on our Site, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.Certain portions of the website and/or all or portions of certain mobile versions of the website and mobile sites may be separately dedicated to, partitioned for, or segregated for purposes of information or uses pertaining specifically to Alpha Epsilon Phi Foundation.  Accordingly, certain information may be collected and used by Alpha Epsilon Phi Foundation, but not by Alpha Epsilon Phi Sorority, Inc. This Privacy Policy answers these questions:What Personal Information Is Collected Through Our Site and Social Media Pages, and How Is It Used?What Information Do We Share with Third Parties?What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Use of Your Personal Information?What Is Our Policy Regarding Children?How Does Our Site Interact with Third-Party Websites and Content?How Will We Update Our Privacy Policy?How Do We Protect and Secure Your Personal Information?Where Should You Direct Your Questions or Concerns?1.  What Personal Information Is Collected Through Our Site and Social Media Pages, and How Is It Used?Information You Provide:  Our Site includes features that allow you to provide personal information to us, such as registering to use certain features and services, paying your dues, contacting us or submitting inquiries to us, or choosing to receive AEPhi information or other communications.  Personal information collected may include name, address, email address, telephone number, demographic information, member or alumnae information, and donation information.We may allow you to use your personal social media account on social media sites (“Personal Social Media Account”) to provide information to us when you participate in certain features on our Site.  This information may include any information you have shared on your Personal Social Media Accounts, such as name, profile picture, gender, list of friends, language, birthday, likes, address, and education.It is also possible that we will be able to continue collecting this information from your Personal Social Media Accounts should the information be revised by you later.  You may choose not to provide us with certain requested information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of the features on our Site.Use of Information:  We use information received through our Site to:Deliver products and services to you;Deliver communications to you that we think you may be interested in;Fulfill your requests;Operate and improve our Site and other services;Create aggregated and anonymized information to determine which features are popular and useful to users, and for other statistical analyses;§  Analyze your activity with us, including interaction with our Site; and/or§  Respond to any inquiries you may have. Cookies and Other Similar Technology:  We and our third-party service providers may use “cookies.”  Cookies assign a unique identification to your device and are typically stored on your device by your web browser.  We may also use pixel tags (also known as web beacons, web bugs, and clear GIFs) on the Site and in emails.
A pixel tag is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a webpage or in an email message.The information we and our third-party service providers collect through cookies, pixel tags, and similar technology includes the following:§  your interactions with our Site;§  the time of your visit to our Site; and§  confirmation of when you open email from us, including the time you open the email and whether you click on any links in the email.We may also use third-party analytics providers to measure traffic and usage trends, and to help us better understand your use of and interaction with the Site.  You can learn about Google’s practices at http://www.google.com/policies..., and opt out by using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpag....The social media sites where we have our Social Media Pages may provide aggregate information and analysis to us about visitors to our Social Media Pages.  This allows us to better understand and analyze our user growth on, general demographic information about the users of our Social Media Pages, and interaction with content on our Social Media Pages.Processing and Storage in the United States:  We store and process personal information in the United States.  Our third-party service providers may also store and process your personal information in the United States.  Such personal information may be subject to disclosure under the laws of the United States.
If you have questions about this processing or storage, please contact us, using one of the options provided below. 2.   What Information Do We Share with Third Parties?Your information may be shared among Alpha Epsilon Phi Sorority, Inc., Alpha Epsilon Phi Foundation, and their respective affiliated and related entities.  We also may share your information with third-party service providers so that they can provide information to help us provide services, such as processing payments, fulfilling orders, monitoring Site activity, providing analytics, fulfilling your requests, marketing our services, hosting the Site, and administering and monitoring emails.Additionally, your information may be shared with and disclosed to unaffiliated third parties in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business assets or merge with another company or are involved in a corporate reorganization or other change of control.  Your personal information may be one of the business assets transferred, shared, or sold as a part of the transaction.We may also disclose your personal information without your consent if we believe, in our sole discretion, it is reasonable to do so to satisfy laws or government regulations, comply with legal process or law enforcement requests, or to protect the rights, safety, or property of AEPhi, our users, or others.3.   What Choices Do You Have Regarding the Use of Your Personal Information?Email:  If you wish to stop receiving emails from us, please follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or contact us at webmaster@aephi.org.Cookies:  You may set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to not accept certain cookies.  However, if you decide not to accept cookies from our Site, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features on our Site.4.   What Is Our Policy Regarding Children?Our Site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly collect information provided by children under the age of 13.5.   How Does Our Site Interact with Third-Party Websites and Content?For your convenience, we may enable you to navigate to third-party sites through links in our Site.  We do not endorse these third-party sites, do not have any affiliation with these third-party sites, and do not control and are not responsible for their Internet and web practices.  Whether the third-party content appears within our Site environment (like a map frame), or you leave our Site for another website to view it, the terms, conditions, and privacy policies of those other websites govern your online experience.  Please review their separate terms of use and service and privacy policies if you have any questions about their practices.6.   How Will We Update Our Privacy Policy?We may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it periodically.  We will update the effective date of the Privacy Policy at the time a change is made.7.   How Do We Protect and Secure Your Personal Information?We employ physical, technical, and administrative procedures to safeguard the personal information we collect through the Site.  While we use these security measures on our Site, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.8.   Where Should You Direct Your Questions or Concerns?If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By email: webmaster@aephi.orgBy postal mail: 11 Lake Avenue Extension, Suite 1A, Danbury, CT 06811By phone: 203-748-0029
